So if you
want to know the complete details of your bike, car or scooter by its number,
like from where did you buy it, on
which date did you buy it, or
what is its insurance status, till when will the insurance be
valid, when will it expire,
or till when is the validity of pollution certificate,
complete details, if you
want to see the complete details of your bike or car, then
where can you see it, in today's
video I am going to tell you the complete step by step, so
if you also want to know, then keep
watching without doing these steps, let's
start the video, so friends, if
you want to check the complete details of your bike, car or scooter by its number,
what do you have to do to see it in your mobile,
first of all you have to download an app
and what is its name, I will
tell you that in the end of this video and here
I will tell you done friends, for this I
downloaded many apps but none was
working well, but this app is
working very well, so I will
tell you its name and email, so let me first of all
I will show you how to
check it and here I will tell you that to
check it, first of all you have to
download it and
after downloading you have to open it and
as you open it you will get to see something like this
and as you can see here
enter bicycle number so here you have to
enter your bike number so
I enter any one
number here and
after entering you can see here search
bicycle so you have to click here
and after clicking here you
can see here something like this will be added here
so you have to cross it and as you
close it you can see here that the
complete details of the vehicle are given here so
when you bought it is also given here
you can see that here either the
pollution status, till when will its validity remain
that is also given here or till
when will the validity of the insurance remain
that is also given here or the complete details of the
bike  If you
want to see the details, you can see them clearly from here. In
this way, you
can check the complete details on your mobile. Now,
I will tell you here which app you
can use to see this. So, what you have to do for that is
first of all, open the Play Store
and then click
here and type RTO Bicycle
Information App and as you type, search
and after searching, you have to
bring it up a little and after that, you can see here,
you have to
download this app and downloading another app will
not work for you. You have to
download this app only and as you download it, then
open it and after opening it,
you have to enter the vehicle number
here and after that, by
searching, you will get to know the complete details. So, in
this way, you can find out. So
friends, I hope this video was
helpful for you. If you liked the video, then
like, comment and share it and to
get such helpful videos,
please subscribe to our channel. So,
friends, see you next day.  Bye bye, thank you in the video till then